{"data":[{"question":"We'll wait until she ________.","a":"arrive","b":"arrives","c":"will arrive","d":"shall arrive","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Future present tense until + simple present tense.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Call Jack as soon as you ________ in town.","a":"get","b":"gets","c":"will get","d":"shall get","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Future present tense until \/when\/as soon as+ simple present tense.\u00a0\n- This sentence implies future tense.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"He knows he has ________ when he is asked to appear on TV.","a":"arrived","b":"arrives","c":"will arrive","d":"shall arrive","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: Have\/has +pp.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"I'll think about your suggestion while I ________ for you.","a":"am waiting","b":"will wait","c":"wait","d":"waits","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense\/future tense + while + simple present continuous.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Before Jack leaves New York, he ________ several new plays.","a":"see","b":"saw","c":"has seen","d":"had seen","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: We use the Present Perfect to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"They will be very happy when they ________ the news.","a":"hear","b":"will hear","c":"heard","d":"has heard","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Future present tense until \/when\/as soon as+ simple present tense.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"I always ________ better after I have rested a while.","a":"feel","b":"feels","c":"will feel","d":"has felt","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: Use the Simple Present to express the idea that an action is repeated or usual (always).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"We will have learned many new words before we ________ through this course.","a":"have got","b":"got","c":"get","d":"will get","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Future present tense until \/when\/as soon as\/ before + simple present tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"It is two o'clock, and I ________ my homework yet.","a":"haven't finished","b":"didn't finish","c":"hadn't finished","d":"don't finish","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: We often use the Present Perfect to say that an action which we expected has not happened. Using the Present Perfect suggests that we are still waiting for the action to happen.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"We usually go out to dinner when we ________ late.","a":"work","b":"worked","c":"has worked","d":"had worked","answer":"1","explain":"\n- By the time\/when + present perfect\/simple present tense, simple future tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"}]}